(Leonard:)So, what's going on?
(Raj:)Okay, here's the deal.
(Raj:)Six months ago, my research
testing the predicted composition...
(Raj:)...of trans-Neptunian objects
ran into a dead end.
(Howard:)So?
My visa is only good as long
as I'm employed at the university.
(Raj:)When they find out I've got squat,
they're gonna cut me off.
By the way, when I say "squat,"
I mean "diddlysquat."
(Raj:)I wish I had squat.
(Leonard:)Wait. What have you been doing
for the past six months?
(Raj:)You know, checking e-mail...
(Raj:)...updating my Facebook status...
(Raj:)...messing up Wikipedia entries.
(Raj:)Did you know Netflix lets you
stream movies on your computer now?
(Sheldon:)You've continued to take the university's
money under false pretenses?
(Sheldon:)Highly unethical for an astrophysicist.
(Sheldon:)Although, practically mandatory
for a pirate.
I don't wanna go back to India.
It's hot and loud.
(Raj:)And there's so many people.